<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE Archive SYSTEM "https://greenstone.org/dtd/Archive/1.0/Archive.dtd">
<Archive>
<Section>
  <Description>
    <Metadata name="gsdlsourcefilename">import\band_members\rob_bourdon.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="gsdlsourcefilerenamemethod">url</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="gsdldoctype">indexed_doc</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Plugin">HTMLPlugin</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="FileSize">5749</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Source">rob_bourdon.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="SourceFile">rob_bourdon.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Language">en</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Encoding">windows_1252</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Title">Rob Bourdon: Biography and Career Overview</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="FileFormat">HTML</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="URL">http://band_members/rob_bourdon.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="UTF8URL">http://band_members/rob_bourdon.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Creator">Petar Milchevski</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Order">5</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Subject">Linkin Park |Band Members</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Title">Rob Bourdon</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Identifier">HASH014333d0161fde1203cd918f</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="lastmodified">1726242806</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="lastmodifieddate">20240913</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="oailastmodified">1727136627</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="oailastmodifieddate">20240924</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="assocfilepath">HASH0143.dir</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="gsdlassocfile">RobB.jfif:unknown:</Metadata>
  </Description>
  <Content>
&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;3&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;20%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;20%&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;
                &lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
                    &lt;font size=&quot;4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rob Bourdon: A Journey Through His Life and Career&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;img src=&quot;_httpdocimg_/RobB.jfif&quot; alt=&quot;Linkin Park Logo&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; width: 75%; height: 75%&quot;&gt;

            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;20%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;60%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;60%&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Early Life&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Robert Gregory Bourdon, known as Rob Bourdon, was born on January 20, 1979, in Calabasas, California. Growing up in a musically inclined family, Rob developed an early interest in drumming. He began playing drums at the age of 10 and quickly showed a natural talent for rhythm and percussion. His passion for music was nurtured during his school years, where he played in various local bands and honed his drumming skills.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Education and Early Music Career&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Rob attended Agoura High School in Agoura Hills, California, where he met future Linkin Park members Mike Shinoda, Brad Delson, and Joe Hahn. Together, they formed the band Xero, which eventually evolved into Linkin Park. Rob's drumming was a key element of the band's early sound, and his rhythm and beats played a crucial role in shaping their musical style. After high school, Rob and his bandmates continued to develop their music, leading to the formation of Linkin Park.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joining Linkin Park&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Rob Bourdon was one of the founding members of Linkin Park, which was formed in 1996. As the band's drummer, Rob brought a powerful and dynamic rhythm to their music. His contributions were instrumental in the creation of Linkin Park's distinctive sound, combining rock, hip-hop, and electronic elements. The band's debut album, &quot;Hybrid Theory,&quot; released in 2000, was a massive success and established Rob and his bandmates as major figures in the music industry.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role in the Band:&lt;/strong&gt; Drummer&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notable Works:&lt;/strong&gt; &quot;In the End,&quot; &quot;Numb,&quot; &quot;Bleed It Out&quot;&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Albums:&lt;/strong&gt; &quot;Hybrid Theory,&quot; &quot;Meteora,&quot; &quot;Minutes to Midnight,&quot; &quot;A Thousand Suns&quot;&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Career with Linkin Park&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Throughout his career with Linkin Park, Rob Bourdon has been known for his technical skill and versatility as a drummer. His rhythmic patterns and powerful drumming have been a key element of the band's energetic live performances. Rob has also been involved in the band's songwriting and production processes, contributing to their musical evolution and success.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live Performances:&lt;/strong&gt; Known for his high-energy drumming and engaging stage presence.&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Studio Work:&lt;/strong&gt; Contributed to the production and recording of multiple Linkin Park albums.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Personal Life&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Rob Bourdon is married to his longtime partner, and the couple has two children. Outside of music, Rob enjoys spending time with his family and is an avid fan of various sports. Despite his success, Rob is known for his down-to-earth personality and dedication to his family life.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Philanthropy and Other Interests&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Rob Bourdon has been actively involved in philanthropic efforts through Linkin Park's charity organization, Music for Relief. This organization focuses on disaster relief and environmental causes, reflecting Rob's commitment to making a positive impact through his music and personal contributions. Rob's involvement in charitable activities demonstrates his dedication to using his platform for good.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Legacy and Impact&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Rob Bourdon's contributions to Linkin Park and his role as a drummer have made a significant impact on the music industry. His innovative drumming and dedication to the band's sound have helped Linkin Park become one of the most influential rock bands of the 21st century. Rob's work continues to inspire drummers and musicians, highlighting the importance of rhythm and percussion in modern music.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;60%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;


</Content>
</Section>
</Archive>
