<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE Archive SYSTEM "https://greenstone.org/dtd/Archive/1.0/Archive.dtd">
<Archive>
<Section>
  <Description>
    <Metadata name="gsdlsourcefilename">import\linkin_park_interesting_facts.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="gsdlsourcefilerenamemethod">url</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="gsdldoctype">indexed_doc</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Plugin">HTMLPlugin</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="FileSize">4850</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Source">linkin_park_interesting_facts.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="SourceFile">linkin_park_interesting_facts.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Language">en</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Encoding">windows_1252</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Title">Interesting Facts About Linkin Park</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="FileFormat">HTML</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="URL">http://linkin_park_interesting_facts.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="UTF8URL">http://linkin_park_interesting_facts.html</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Subject">Linkin Park </Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Identifier">HASH01e9f3094586ae30edb1a1e6</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="lastmodified">1726239033</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="lastmodifieddate">20240913</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="oailastmodified">1726242855</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="oailastmodifieddate">20240913</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="assocfilepath">HASH01e9.dir</Metadata>
  </Description>
  <Content>
&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;3&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;20%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;20%&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;
                &lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
                    &lt;font size=&quot;4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interesting Facts About Linkin Park&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
                &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;20%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;60%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;60%&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;1. Origin of the Band Name&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Linkin Park was originally named Xero when it was formed in 1996. The band changed their name to Linkin Park in 1999, inspired by Lincoln Park in Santa Monica, California. They altered the spelling to avoid legal issues with the name.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;2. Record-Breaking Debut&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The band's debut album, &quot;Hybrid Theory,&quot; released in 2000, is one of the best-selling debut albums of the 21st century. It has been certified Diamond by the RIAA and Multi-Platinum by various international certifications.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;3. Genre-Mixing Innovators&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Linkin Park is known for their unique blend of rock, hip-hop, and electronic music. They were among the pioneers in combining these genres, which played a significant role in the development of the nu-metal genre.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;4. Grammy Awards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Linkin Park won their first Grammy Award in 2002 for Best Hard Rock Performance for their song &quot;Crawling&quot; from the &quot;Hybrid Theory&quot; album. They have received multiple Grammy nominations and wins throughout their career.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;5. Philanthropic Efforts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The band established Music for Relief, a non-profit organization dedicated to disaster relief and environmental conservation. They have been involved in various relief efforts, including fundraising for disaster-stricken areas and supporting eco-friendly initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;6. Virtual Concert Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;In 2020, Linkin Park held a virtual concert to celebrate the 20th anniversary of their &quot;Hybrid Theory&quot; album. The concert featured live performances and exclusive content, providing fans with a unique online experience during the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;7. Iconic Music Videos&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The music video for &quot;In the End&quot; has become iconic, featuring a blend of live-action and animation. It was one of the band's most popular videos and played a significant role in their rise to fame.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;8. Diverse Musical Collaborations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Linkin Park has collaborated with a variety of artists across different genres. Notable collaborations include songs with Jay-Z, Steve Aoki, and Kiiara, showcasing their versatility and willingness to experiment with different musical styles.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;9. Impact on Video Games&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The band's music has been featured in several video games, including the popular &quot;Fortnite&quot; and &quot;Medal of Honor&quot; series. Their songs often enhance the gaming experience with high-energy tracks and immersive soundtracks.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;10. Record-Breaking Tours&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Linkin Park's tours have been some of the highest-grossing tours in the rock genre. Their performances are known for their high energy and elaborate stage setups, drawing large crowds and earning critical acclaim.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td height=&quot;60%&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;


</Content>
</Section>
</Archive>
